Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU); Records apap046
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1972-1985; 7
  This series contains SASU's regular publications, Update (1972-77, 1981-85), and Grassroots, (1978-81), special issues such as the SASU Voter Information 1976, and People's University (1975), and a couple of issues of SASU Weekly, (1979). It also contains posters of events organized or sponsored by SASU.
  - Grassroots, 1978-1980 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
  - People's Unbiversity, 1975 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
  - People's Weekly, 1979 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
  - SASU Update, 1972-1977; 1981-1985 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
  - SASU Voter Information, 1976 (Box 1 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
- Political Posters, 1972-1984; 8
  This series includes posters used at rallies by members of SASU. Topics covered include presidential and gubernatorial candidates, opposition to the Vietnam War, support for the environment, anti-Apartheid sentiment, as well as other issues.
  - Abolish Laws That Murder Women, 1979 January 20 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - The Student Association of The State University of New York Money Problems, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - The Student Association of The State University of New York Reciprocity of Student Activities, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - Defend Public Higher Education, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - Health Fee To Be Repealed SASU, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - March and Lobby Jobs for Youth, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - Fight The Hike! SASU, 1981 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - Support A Strong Statewide Student Voice SASU, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - Will you be able to Afford a SUNY Education?, 1984 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - SASU Foundation Internship Program, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - SASU Tripled Rooms, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - Education is our Right 540,000 Students is Our Might Students Unite, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - SASU Entertain, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - The Student Voice Rally on The Capital, 1979 March 19 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 1)
  - SASU: Can we afford to do without it?, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Isn't it About time the Board of Trustees had a few Students SASU, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - All members of the University have equal rights and privileges right? Wrong. Some of us are students. SASU, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Sharon Ward an Experienced Leader Student Association President, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - SASU Studentrek, 1975 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Rally on The Capital Stop The Tuition Increase, 1979 March 21 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - The United States Student Association Certifies SASU as a member of the Association, 1981 February 6 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - SASU Recognition For All Of Us Now, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Student Population 1950 - 1980, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - 55,000 voters won't make it to the polls this year, Universities National Anti War Fund, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Let People Live Support The Peoples Peace Treaty, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Make Your Own Peace, North South Vietnam Fund, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Operation Dewey Canyon 3, Vietnam Veterans Against the War, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Orange Composition, Support for the NLF and the Vietnamese People, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 2)
  - Phase 1: Nixon Eviction, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - Pull Him Out Now, Anti War Rally, April 24, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - We The People Declare Peace, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - You May Fool All The People Some Of The TimeMarch On Washington, Anti-War Rally, April 24, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - March 24: International Day of Solidarity With...Portugal, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - National Week Of Action In Support Of African Liberation Movements, April 4-11, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - The Mass'ah Is Alive And Well In South Africa, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - National Student Lobby, Congressional Record, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - March On Washington For A Non Nuclear World, April 26, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - If Your Doctor Signs On The Left Side Ask Why, NYPIRG, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - McGovern For President, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - Hands That Pick Cotton Now Can Pick Our Public Officials, [1976] (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 3)
  - Remember In November: Vote CCSA, [1976] (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - How Far Will You Go? Save SUNY, Jan. 29, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Hundreds Of Jobs Are Hanging By A Thread, Save SUNY, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - The Blade Is About To Fall, Save SUNY, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Remember Me Remember The Stevens Workers, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Support Justice For Textile Workers, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Testimony: Justice vs J.P. Stevens, 1977 May 17 (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Saving Energy, Saving Jobs: Hugh Carey, Governor, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Support Mother Earth, Rally May 14, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Stop Baby Bottle Disease, Clip Nestle Quik, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Fed Up With Inflation: Send Your Bills To Congress, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Take the Health Fee Out of the SUNY Budget, Undated (Box 1 (8-Political Posters), Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees 5 Million in TAP Adjustments, Sheet, Undated (Box 2 (8-Political Posters))